ABISERCK MATHANASEGAR

18 A Bodhirukkarama Road Kalubowila Dehiwala.

Email: - abiserck5@gmail.com

Mobile: - +94 779618406



PERSONAL SUMMERY

A highly competent and organized systems administrator with experience of software procurement, installation, administration & compatibility. Possessing a proven ability to assist with the day-to-day running of an IT department and its business IT systems. Extensive knowledge of monitoring and controlling data security within guidelines to ensure compliance and report on possible improvements.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

October 2012 – July 2015 SYSTEM ADMINISTRTOR

7STORIES RANJANAS (PVT) Ltd

Colombo/Kandy, Srilanka

December 2010 – September 2012 IT Executive

Cloud Lanka, Colombo, Srilanka

PROFESSIONL QUALIFICATIONS

3 200-120: CCNA Cisco Certified Network Associate September 30, 2015

3 Following Microsoft Certification Exams Completed Successfully:

70-646 Pro: Windows Server 2008, Server Administrator August 26, 2011

70-640 TS: Windows Server 2008 Active Directory, Configuring July 04, 2011

70-642 TS: Windows Server 2008 Network Infrastructure, Configuring April 04, 2011

70-643 TS: Windows Server 2008, Application Infrastructure Configuring Sep 27, 2011

70- 647 Pro: Windows Server 2008, Enterprise Administrator September 29, 2011

70-680 TS: Windows 7, **Configuring** June 12, 2010

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

2012 – 2013 BSc (Hons) in Network & Mobile Computing

Coventry University, UK.

2009 – 2010 Higher National Diploma in ICT System Support (Edexcel)

IDM Nations Campus, Srilanka.

2007-2009 Diploma in Computer Engineering

FTMS GLOBAL, Singapore.

2001-2006 G.C.E (O/L)

St.John's College, Srilanka.

SKILLS AND QUALITIES

- 3 Experience with MS Windows 2003/2008/2012 Server, XP/Windows 7/Windows 8 O/S.
- 3 Experience with Microsoft Dynamic NAV 2009.
- 3 Experience with Cisco Routers and switch
- 3 Experience with SQL Server 2012, Databases
- Strong knowledge in hardware assembling and Disassembling and Installing OS & NOS.
- 3 Good troubleshooting skills
- 3 Excellent communication and interpersonal skills.
- 3 Ability to work in teams and autonomously/independently.
- 3 Ability to work under pressure in critical situations.
- 3 Strong believer of working towards meeting the deadline.
- 3 Have led dynamic youth team in Leoism.
- 3 Willingness to travel.

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- 3 An active member of Leo Club of Colombo Circle Leo District 306B2 from 2010
 - Multiple District Treasurer Leo Multiple District 306, Sri Lanka fiscal year 2015/2016
 - **District President** Leo District 306 B2 For the Fiscal Year **2014/2015**
 - **District Vice President** Leo District 306B2 for the Fiscal Year **2013/2014**.
 - Club President for the fiscal year 2012/2013 and have been chosen the Best President of the year 2012/2013.
 - Club Vice President for the fiscal year 2011 / 2012 and have been chosen the Best Vice President of the year 2011/2012.
 - Chosen as the **Best Leo of the year** over 1000 Leos in district in consecutive year 2011/2012 and 2012/2013.
- 3 Worked on various community awareness projects and teams.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name with Initials : M.Abiserck

Full Name : Abiserck Mathanasegar

Postal Address : 18 A Bodhirukkarama Road Kalubowila Dehiwala.

Date of Birth : 05-11-1990

Sex : Male

Civil status : Single

Nationality : Sri Lankan

Contact : 0094 779618406

Email Address : abiserck5@gmail.com

REFEREES

1. Miss Abarnah Kirupananda [MSc]

Lecturer

Informatics Institute of Technology

57, Ramakrishna Road, Colombo 06

Tel: - 009411 2360212, 0094718270423

Email: Abarnah.k@iit.ac.lk

2. Mr A.Thusyanthan [B.Eng]

Tech Lead

IronOne Technologies (PVT) Ltd.

465/7, Galle Road, colombo-06

Tel: - 0094 775024666

Email: athusy@gmail.com